mymoneyblog.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Policy » My Money Blog - Personal Finance and Investing Blog

I don’t sell your information or spam you. You can sign up for site updates or even updates to specific posts if you wish, but you must opt-in and you can cancel at any time. I do have a “web counter” that measures how many people visit my site, but it does not record any personally-identifiable information.

**MyMoneyBlog.com Privacy Policy:**

This site respects privacy of Internet Users and does not collect personally identifying information without the Internet User’s permission.

**Collection of Data**  
This site does not collect identity or contact information from Internet Users to this website. This site may however, collect non-personally identifiable information, for example, browser type, operating system, domain name, time spent on the web site, or referring link. This is done via a “counter” by sites like Google Analytics or Statcounter.com

_This site does not sell or rent personally identifying information._ This site does not disclose personally identifying information to anyone that is not authorized to do so. This site uses anonymous user data to create and report the browsing, purchasing and/or lead form completion activities of anonymous users.

This site reserves the right to release information on Internet Users if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. Disclosure shall be limited to only to those we are compelled to disclose to. At present, all information processing occurs in the United States.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites**  
This site contains links to other Internet websites and has no control or authority over the information submitted/collected by these third party website(s). Please refer to the respective Privacy Policy of the individual third party website(s).

**Use and Disclosure of Data**

**Spam**

This site does not intentionally send unsolicited e-mail messages that could legitimately be construed as spam.

**COPPA**  
This site complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. This site is not specifically directed to children under 18. If this site has been informed or unintentionally collected or received information from a child under 18, we will immediately delete such information from our databases. This site shall not knowingly distribute any personally identifiable information erroneously collected from children under 18.

**Policy Changes**  
With or without prior notification, we may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. All changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by us prior to the effective date of the policy change.
